[Music]
[Encouraging voice]
Hey my head is full Hey
brother, let's hurry up my head is torn, the
ground is torn, brother, brother, there is a
lot of sorrow
Hey Babu, peace too, buy a
saree,
buy a cheap saree
[Music]
Hey
[Music] Saree, which patta saree, brother, what's the
fun [Music] Bakad
[Music]
Which saree, the saree is torn,
look at the
saree, all the latest collection, the
complete original silk saree, number one work,
see the look of the design, I
agree with you, sorry, sorry, brother, the complete I agree,
only 10,000 rupees, please sell me,
10,000 rupees, this
Kanjeevaram saree, the complete South Indian
style saree, only 5,000 rupees,
Babu, have you seen the South North, have you
seen any khati saree, I mean, look at Salpuri, this Salpuri
silk saree, the complete one quality rate is only
2500 rupees,
see the saree, it is not cheap, what
rate, you can see it,
even if you have
free time [Music]
Look lady  Customer
saree
5000 rupees I will give you saree Even if I buy saree, I don't have the status I don't have the status
Hey, which shop is for
saree, settle down, settle down Hey, did you see the saree in the house,
look at the saree,
you too are
not a saree, all the goods are
Babu Babu, no, it is not this, no, no,
who, no, no, no, look at the couple, do not look at the saree on the table, do steal, see, steal, see,
Babu, open your dress and check, steal
[music]
[laughs] The
shop is looking for saree, I am
not keeping the saree, women, your saree is lying, where is it, hey brother, tell me where is the saree, hey, where [music] [voice of singing] Babu, hit him with his full hand, haven't you
seen the camera,
hey, you have completely forgotten
[music] [
music]
Oh God, the world is in a hurry
[music]
[music] Hey, hey, let it
fly away
[music]
Hey, hey, hey, hey, she is a woman, is she stealing,
stop, police,
go
[laughs]
too
[music]
[laughs]
Hey, saree, hey, it is not a saree, take the saree
[music]
Look, the
saree is
empty
[screaming  [Voice]
Lo
my street, lo stoned, if
you see the
girl,
Swami is not trapped, if the
master is empty, then he is shocked, hey Ruha Ruha, this
story of my heart is not quenched, but I will not be able to do it,
[Music]
Hey Mother, forgive me, I have forgotten someone, then
go to the shop, my friend
[Music]
Hum